(Leonard:)I'm the one
who thought of it!
(Penny:)Well, didn't he do
a lot of the work?
(Leonard:)But now he's happy
to let people think
(Leonard:)he's responsible for everything.
(Penny:)And that's why you get
an iPad helicopter!
(Sheldon:)Is it my fault I have a much
bigger reputation than he does?
(Amy:)It's not your fault.
(Sheldon:)Is it my fault
that my name came first
(Sheldon:)on the paper alphabetically?
(Amy:)Not your fault.
(Sheldon:)Is it my fault
that when the reporter cited me
(Sheldon:)as the lead scientist
I didn't correct him?
(Amy:)Hey, look at that pretty bird.
(Leonard:)He always needs
all the attention.
(Leonard:)He's such a baby.
(Penny:)I know, I know.
(Leonard:)I swear, he is never ever
playing with my helicopter.
(Raj:)Okay, I'll start heating
some of this stuff up.
(Howard:)Thanks.
(Howard:)Oh, man.
(Howard:)This is the boutonniere
from my high school prom...
(chuckles)
(Howard:)...a piece of cake
from my Bar Mitzvah.
(Bernadette:)Did she throw
anything away?